{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The entity integrity rule states that:", "opta": "no primary key attribute may be null.", "optb": "no primary key can be composite.", "optc": "no primary key may be unique.", "optd": "no primary key may be equal to a value in a foreign key.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a many-to-many unary relationship into a relation which of the following is true?", "opta": "One relation is created.", "optb": "Two relations are created.", "optc": "Three relations are created.", "optd": "Four relations are created.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If no multivalued attributes exist and no partial dependencies exist in a relation, then the relation is in what normal form?", "opta": "First normal form", "optb": "Second normal form", "optc": "Third normal form", "optd": "Fourth normal form", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A foreign key is which of the following?", "opta": "Any attribute", "optb": "The same thing as a primary key", "optc": "An attribute that serves as the primary key of another relation", "optd": "An attribute that serves no purpose", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A transitive dependency is which of the following?", "opta": "A functional dependency between two or more key attributes.", "optb": "A functional dependency between two or more nonkey attributes.", "optc": "A relation that is in first normal form.", "optd": "A relation that is in second normal form.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a multivalued attribute into a relation which of the following is true?", "opta": "One relation is created.", "optb": "Two relations are created.", "optc": "Three relations are created.", "optd": "Four relations are created.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If no multivalued attributes exist in a relation, then the relation is in what normal form?", "opta": "First normal form", "optb": "Second normal form", "optc": "Third normal form", "optd": "Fourth normal form", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A primary key is which of the following?", "opta": "Any attribute", "optb": "An attribute that uniquely identifies each row", "optc": "An attribute that uniquely identifies each column", "optd": "A derived attribute", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The relational model consists of:", "opta": "data in the form of tables.", "optb": "data redundancy.", "optc": "operations using non-SQL languages.", "optd": "unorganized data.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a binary many-to-many relationship into a relation which of the following is true?", "opta": "One relation is created.", "optb": "Two relations are created.", "optc": "Three relations are created.", "optd": "Four relations are created.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relation has which of the following properties?", "opta": "Each row is not unique.", "optb": "Attributes can have the same name within a given table.", "optc": "Each relation has a unique name.", "optd": "The order of the columns is significant.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a ternary relationship with an associative entity into a relation which of the following is true?", "opta": "One relation is created.", "optb": "Two relations are created.", "optc": "Three relations are created.", "optd": "Four relations are created.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a regular entity into a relation which of the following is true?", "opta": "One relation is created.", "optb": "Two relations are created.", "optc": "Three relations are created.", "optd": "Four relations are created.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When mapping a supertype/subtype relationship which of the following is true?", "opta": "The supertype primary key is assigned to each subtype.", "optb": "The subtype primary key is assigned to each supertype.", "optc": "There is no link between the supertype/subtype entities.", "optd": "There is no primary key/foreign key relationship between a supertype/subtype.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Relations are:", "opta": "two-dimensional tables.", "optb": "three-dimensional tables.", "optc": "four-dimensional tables.", "optd": "five-dimensional tables.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}